

CONTACT ME

- **(** 09958233004
- rheyaaron802@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/rhe y-rhey-de-mesa-a438892a4/
- 6 7th Avenue Cubao Quezon City, Philippines

EDUCATION

Polytechnic University of the Philippines

BS Computer Engineering completed in 2023

Technological Institute of the Philippines

Senior Highschool completed in 2019

Ramon Magsaysay (Cubao) Highschool

Junior Highschool completed in 2017

Ramon Magsaysay (Cubao) Highschool

completed in 2013

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML5/ TailwindCSS
- ReactJS
- Phyton
- Java
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator

Rhey-Rhey De Mesa

ABOUT ME

I am a 23-year-old graduate student who completed a Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering at Polytechnic University of the Philippines. I am a artistic person and I earned money through commission graphic design work during nearly my entire time in engineering school. I saw some similarities when I recreate some design in photoshop and making a website following a specific design and making it's functionalities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

RadiantMinds Professional Solutions I Social Media Specialist

August 2022 - October 2022

Key responsibilities

- Daily monitoring of engagement of the activities done in the company's social media
- Creating digital posters to engage audiences by conveying information in a visually compelling and dynamic manner.

Freelance Graphic Designer

2021-2022

Key responsibilities

- Conceptualizing visual, by developing creative concepts and ideas for visual communication, considering the project's goals and target audience
- Make visually appealing and practical designs, such as logos, content for social media, and other graphic elements
- Utilize graphic design software such as Adobe Creative Suite (e.g., Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign) to bring concepts to life.

Freelance Visual Content Creator

2020-2021

Key responsibilities

- Ensure consistency in design elements and adhere to brand guidelines across various platforms and materials
- Effectively communicate design concepts and rationale to clients or team members, incorporating feedback to refine and improve designs.

AFFILIATIONS

FAO Dance Crew

2022-2023

Creatives and design head